<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Setting a label</title>
    <author>Shinsuke Sugaya</author>
  </properties>
  <body><p style="font-weight:bold;color:red;">This page is generated by Machine Translation from Japanese.</p>
    <section name='Overview'>
      <p>Here are settings for the label. Label can classify documents that appear in search results, select the crawl settings in. You can pass even if you do not set the crawl settings in the settings of the label to add labels to specify regular expressions. If you register the label shown select label drop-down box to the right of the search box.</p>
    </section>
    <section name='How to set up'>
      <subsection name='How to display'>
        <p>In Administrator account after logging in, click the menu label.</p>
        <img alt='List of labels' src='/images/en/9.3/admin/labelType-1.png'/>
        <img alt='Setting a label' src='/images/en/9.3/admin/labelType-2.png'/>
      </subsection>
    </section>
    <section name='Setting item'>
      <subsection name='Display name'>
        <p>Specifies the name that is displayed when the search label drop-down select.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Value'>
        <p>Specifies the identifier when a classified document. This value will be sent to Solr. Must be alphanumeric characters.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Path to crawl'>
        <p>Sets the path to label in the regular expression. You can specify multiple in multiple line description. Notwithstanding the crawl configuration document to match the path specified here, will be labeled.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='The path to exclude from being crawled'>
        <p>In the path and crawled on regular expressions set from what you want to exclude. You can specify multiple in multiple line description.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Roll'>
        <p>Specifies the role to view the label.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Display order'>
        <p>Specifies the order of the labels.</p>
      </subsection>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
