<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Appearance settings</title>
    <author>Shinsuke Sugaya</author>
  </properties>
  <body>
    <section name='Overview'>
      <p>Here are settings for the design of search screens.</p>
    </section>
    <section name='How to set up'>
      <subsection name='How to display'>
        <p>In Administrator account after logging in, click the menu design.</p>
        <img alt='Design' src='/images/ja/9.0/admin/design-1.png'/>
        <p>You can edit the search screen in the screen below.</p>
        <img alt='JSP compilation screen' src='/images/ja/9.0/admin/design-2.png'/>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='To view the registration date and modified date'>
        <p>If you want to display in the search results crawl in Fess and registered or modified files to get the search results page (content), write the following.</p>
      <source><![CDATA[
<fmt:formatDate value="${fe:parseDate(doc.lastModified)}" pattern="yyyy-MM-dd" />
]]></source>
        <p>tstampDate will crawl during registration on the lastModifiedDate modified date of the document. Output date formats follow the fmt:formateDate specification.</p>
      </subsection>
    </section>
    <section name='Setting item'>
      <subsection name='File management'>
        <p>On the search screen files are available to download and can be removed.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='File upload'>
        <p>You can upload the file to use in the search screen. Image file names are supported are jpg, gif, png, css, and js.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='File name'>
        <p>Use if you want to specify the file name file to upload. Uploaded if you omit the file name will be used.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Design JSP files'>
        <p>You can edit the JSP files in the search screen. You can by pressing the Edit button of the JSP file, edit the current JSP files. And pressing the button will default to edit as a JSP file when you install. To keep with the update button in the Edit screen, changes are reflected.</p>
        <p>Following are examples of how to write.</p>
        <table class='table table-striped table-bordered table-condensed' columninfo='lp{10cm}'>
          <caption>JSP file that you can edit</caption>
          <tbody>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Top page (frame)</td>
              <td align='left'>Is a JSP file search home page. This JSP include JSP file of each part.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Header</td>
              <td align='left'>It is a JSP file&apos;s header.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Footer</td>
              <td align='left'>This is the footer JSP files.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Search results pages (frames)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search result is a list page of JSP files. This JSP include JSP file of each part.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Search results pages (content)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search results search results list page is a JSP file to represent the part. Is the search results when the JSP file. If you want to customize the search result representation change.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Search results page (result no)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search results search results list page is a JSP file to represent the part. Is a JSP file when the search result is not used.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Help pages (frames)</td>
              <td align='left'>Is the help page of JSP files.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Search error page</td>
              <td align='left'>It is a JSP file search error page. If you want to customize the search error expression change.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Mobile home (frames)</td>
              <td align='left'>It is a JSP file for mobile home. This JSP include JSP file of each part.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Mobile home (within the Head tags)</td>
              <td align='left'>Is a JSP file to express within the head tag for the mobile home page. If you want to edit the meta tags, title tags, script tags, such as the change.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Mobile home (content)</td>
              <td align='left'>Is a JSP file to represent in the body tag of the mobile home.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results pages (frames)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search results for mobile is a JSP file&apos;s page. This JSP include JSP file of each part.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results page (within the Head tags)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search results for mobile is a JSP file to represent within the head tags of the page. If you want to edit the meta tags, title tags, script tags, such as the change.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results page (header)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search results for mobile is a JSP file to represent the header of the page. Include search form at the top.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results page (footer)</td>
              <td align='left'>Search results for mobile is a JSP file that represents the footer part of the page. Contains the copyright page at the bottom.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results pages (content)</td>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results search results page is a JSP file to represent the part. Is the search results when the JSP file. If you want to customize the search result representation change.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results page (result no)</td>
              <td align='left'>Portable search results search results page is a JSP file to represent the part. Is a JSP file when the search result is not used.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>File boot page</td>
              <td align='left'>Is the file boot page JSP file. Is the screen used when displaying Java plug-in is enabled to display the search results by using the file system CROLL.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Error page (header)</td>
              <td align='left'>Is a JSP file that represents the header of the page.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Error page (footer)</td>
              <td align='left'>It is a JSP file that represents the footer part of the page.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Error page (page not found)</td>
              <td align='left'>It is displayed if the page cannot be found error page JSP file.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Error (System error)</td>
              <td align='left'>JSP error page that appears if the system error is.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='a'>
              <td align='left'>Error pages (redirects)</td>
              <td align='left'>This is the JSP error page displayed when an HTTP redirect occurs.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr class='b'>
              <td align='left'>Error (bad request)</td>
              <td align='left'>Is the error bad request appears when the JSP file.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>You can to edit for PCs and similar portable screen.</p>
      </subsection>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
