<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Web authentication settings</title>
    <author>Shinsuke Sugaya</author>
  </properties>
  <body>
    <section name='Overview'>
      <p>Describes Web authentication is required when set against here, using Web crawling. Fess is corresponding to a crawl for BASIC authentication and DIGEST authentication.</p>
    </section>
    <section name='How to set up'>
      <subsection name='How to display'>
        <p>In Administrator account after logging in, click menu Web authentication.</p>
        <img alt='Configuring Web authentication' src='/images/ja/9.1/admin/webAuthentication-1.png'/>
      </subsection>
    </section>
    <section name='Setting item'>
      <subsection name='Host name'>
        <p>Specifies the host name of the site that requires authentication. Web crawl settings you specify if applicable in any host name.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Port'>
        <p>Specifies the port of the site that requires authentication. Specify-1 to apply for all ports. Web crawl settings you specified and if applicable on any port.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Realm'>
        <p>Specifies the realm name of the site that requires authentication. Web crawl settings you specify if applicable in any realm name.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Authentication methods'>
        <p>Select the authentication method. You can use BASIC authentication, DIGEST authentication or NTLM authentication.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='User name'>
        <p>Specifies the user name to log in authentication.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Password'>
        <p>Specifies the password to log into the certification site.</p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Parameter'>
        <p>Sets if the authentication site login required settings. You can set the workstation and domain values for NTLM authentication. If you want to write as.</p>
        <source><![CDATA[
workstation=HOGE
domain=FUGA
]]></source>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name='Web name'>
        <p>Select to apply the above authentication settings Web settings name. Must be registered in advance Web crawl settings.</p>
      </subsection>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
